Riccardo Reali

Contact

Address

Toronto, canada

Phone

6479018936

E-mail

riccardoreali05@gmail.com

Skills

Cpr and First Aid Multitask and Organizational Skills

Fast Learner Attention to Details

Languages

English

Spanish

Italian

French

Conscientious Customer Service Associate, with experience solving problems creatively and using tact and diplomacy to achieve win-win outcomes. Team player comfortable in competitive, fast-paced environments. Effective in handling direct customer inquiries, and executing financial responsibilities.

Work History

2021-05 -2022-01

Statistics Canada Enumerator

Statistics Canada, Toronto, ON

- Remote work.
- Collected large amount of data.
- Assisted with translation barrier for Spanish and Italian respondents.
- Managed collection data management system.
- Data Entry.
- Attended zoom team meetings.
- Conducted phone and in-person interviews.
- Data entry quality control.
- Met weekly goals set by team leader.
- Handled office administration and forms.

2020-01 -2020-03

Screening Officer

CATSA, Toronto

- Ensured safety of all passengers.
- Screened passengers and luggage.
- Directed passengers to locations and answered their questions.
- Operated screening equipment.
- Made effective decisions to ensure safety under all circumstances.

2018-03 -2019-12

Sales Supervisor

180, Toronto

- Answered phone and customer direct calls as required.
- Managed Inventory.
- Worked along with management and followed directions
- Opening/Closing operations.
- Oversaw employee performance, corrected problems and increased efficiency to maintain productivity targets.
- Strengthened merchandising and promotional strategies to drive customer engagement and boost sales.

2016-02 -2018-02

Store Clerk

Convenient Store, Etobicoke

- Responsible for the filling and delivery of all requisitions for stock items from store
- Provided excellent customer service
- Disinfected display cases, shelves and aisles
- Managed POS transactions
- Received, stored and reported all incoming items
- Created monthly displays to increase sales.
- Assisted customer by locating items, processing payments and carrying out heavy purchases.

2014-09 -2015-10

Hotel Front Desk

Hotel 300, Rome, Italy

- Answered phone calls.
- Assisted guests with general services.
- Checked guests in/out.
- Handled cash and credit cards payments.
- Managed e-mails.
- Responsible for creating a complete report for management.
- Collected room deposits, fees and payments.

2013-07 -2014-07

Cast Member Supervisor

Walt Disney World, Orlando, FL

- Trained new cast members
- Assisted guests with inquiries and complaints
- Managed kiosk inventory
- Helped creating an unforgettable experience for our guests
- Supervised 4 cast members per shift
- Worked as part of the team in daily operation.

Education

High School Diploma

Liceo James Joyce - Italy